Guide to the Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER) Records 2000-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Special Events, 1979-2008
  - Membership Coffees, 1984-1999
    - James Clarke - Dental Implants, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Host: Laura Blanton
    - Joseph Feste - Endometriosis, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Host: Roberta Howell
    - Jackalyn Rainosek - Stress and How it Relates to the Total Woman, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Host: Katsy Mecom
    - Karen Ritchie - Biofeedback and Relaxation, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Host: Mary Jo Hunt
    - Elizabeth Watson - Houston Safety Alert: What You Can Do about Crime, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Host: Sharon Lorenzo
    - Chris C. Steele - A Celebration of Hope in the Season of 'Bright Sadness', 1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Jan Carson - Presentation of 1992 Grants (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Host: Pat Breen
    - Reversing Heart Disease: Is it Possible?, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Host: Odessa Wexler
    - Host: Ginny Mithoff, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 26a)
    - Host: Janice McNair, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 26b)
    - Cheryl Alston - What's Up, Doc, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 26c)
    - Speaker: Raymond Kaufman, MD, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 26d)
  - Professional Women's Luncheons, 1988-1991
    The Professional Women's Luncheons were organized to appeal to working women who might not be able to participate in other Women's Fund events because of career obligations. Women's Fund members and women at a number of Houston corporations and law firms were invited to these luncheons.
    - 1st Annual - Melvyn Schreiber - Diagnostic Techniques for Self-Preservation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - 2nd Annual - Ron Carson - Medical Ethics, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - 3rd Annual - June Levy - Remarriage and Step Families, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - 4th Annual - Travis Peterson - Holiday Stress, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Outreach Events, 1995-1999
    Outreach Events were organized to fill niches of need in the Women's Fund programming. Women's and Girls' Health Day offered a day-long venue of health and wellness programming, including presentations, posters, free consultations with health care educators. Additionally, it offered opportunities for hundreds of Houston area students to compete for cash prizes and college scholarships. A Denim Affair honored a previous benefit luncheon presenter, Janice Woods Windle, on the occasion of the televising of her novel, True Women. The event also served as a fundraiser for the Women's Fund. A celebration luncheon to commemorate the 20th anniversary of the organization was held in 1999. Corporate members and sponsors, individual members and other health-affiliated organizations joined to celebrate 20 years of contribution, education, and progress toward women's issues.
    - Women's and Girls' Health Day, 1995-1999
      - Women's and Girls' Health Day, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Scholarship Essay Contest, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Publicity/Follow-ups, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Sponsors, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Arrangements, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Health Tips/Printing Samples, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Scholarship Essay Contest, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Publicity/Follow-ups, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Sponsors, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Arrangements, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Health Tips/Printing Samples, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Scholarship Essay Contest, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Publicity/Follow-ups, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Sponsors, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Arrangements, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Health Tips/Printing Samples, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Denim Affair, 1997
      - Attendance, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Event/Celebrity Arrangements, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Income/Expenses, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Publicity, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Press Kit folders, undated (Box 9, Folder 35a)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration Luncheon, 1999
      - Committee Minutes/Planning, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Arrangements (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Attendance, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Sponsors, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Publicity/Follow-ups, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Printing Samples (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Rockin' Resiliency Luncheon, 2012
      - Volunteer Organizations, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Event Information, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Logistics, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Speaker Information, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Merchants, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Raffle, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Sponsors and Attendees, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Other Donations, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Thank You's, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Events, 1997-2014
    - Theta Charity Antique Show; 1997-1999 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Harris and Eliza Kempner Fund, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 23rd Annual Benefit Luncheon – Official Gift Receipt, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Spring Fundraiser, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Catering Sales Event Agreement, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rocking Resiliency Host Committee, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Rocking Resiliency - Sponsors, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Rocking Resiliency - Vendors, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Rocking Resiliency - Raffle Prizes, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Rocking Resiliency – Fall Event, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Spring Fundraising Event, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Rocking Resiliency – Shop Vendors, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - YPO Poker Tournament, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Contributions, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Rocking Resiliency – Invoices, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Rocking Resiliency – Misc, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Spring Event, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Matching Gifts Form, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Development Committee, 2011-2012 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Spring Fundraising, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Spring Fundraiser, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Committee Records – Membership Directory, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Other Newsletters and Pamphlets, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Women and Girls' Good Health Day – General, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - National Women's Health Week Webinar Invoice, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - National Women's Health Week – Table Seating Arrangement, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - McGovern Seminar, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer Seminar, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - 30th Anniversary Benefit Luncheon – Sponsorship Agreement, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - New Release & Clippings, 1994-2001 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Reports, 1991-1994; 1999-2002 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Public Relations Memos, Correspondence, 1994-1999; 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Past Events, 1999-2002; 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Speaker's Bureau, 1993-2008
    - Speakers "A" through "W", 1994-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1-21)
    - Speaker Renewals, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Program/Invites, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Speakers' Photos, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Medical Speakers A-L, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Medical Speakers L-W, 1994; 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Speakers - Mental and Other Health Related Issues, 1993-2003 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - CVs, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Placement Reports, 1993-2005 (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
    - Inactive Speakers, 1994-2003 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Speaker Request Form, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Granting Process, 1980-2011
  The Granting Process Series includes all the documents related to the process of announcing, reviewing, and awarding grants for medical and educational research. In 1980, the Women's Fund began funding research grants. Funding for those early grants was modest, but over 18 years, the Women's Fund approved and funded 147 grant applications. Total expended funds for these dates top $1,000,000. Besides formal medical research, the organization funded several outreach service programs with far reaching effects. This series includes three subseries: Grant Administration, Grant Applications, and Research and Review Committee.
  - Grant Administration
    There are four folders in this subseries, which are arranged alphabetically with folder contents arranged chronologically.
    - Grant Applications - Correspondence, 1980-1998 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Grant Review Board, 1980-1996 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Grant Review Committee, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Granting History, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Grant Applications and Processing, 1980-2011
    There are sixty-two folders in this subseries, which are arranged chronologically.
    - Giovanella, B.C. - Tissue Culture of Human Breast Carcinoma, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Fritsche, H. - Immune Complex Detection in Breast Cancer, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Taylor, J. - Computer Requirements for the Breast Research Program, 1980-1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Smith, P.S. - Prevention of Adolescent Pregnancy: Administrative and Clinical Issues, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Kaufman, R. H. - Herpes Relationship to Carcinoma of the Cervix and Vulva, and DES Exposure in Utero and in Cancer, 1980 and 1982 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hays, B. - Baylor Lactation Clinic and 24-hour Hotline for Breast-feeding Mothers, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Hays, B. - Baylor Lactation Clinic and 24-hour Hotline for Breast-feeding Mothers, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Sadowski, B.R. - The Relationship of Testosterone Concentration, Spatial Ability, and Sex Role Identification in Women in Determining Preference for Mathematics as a Teaching Field, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Gordon, C. - Depression and Satisfaction in Varying Combinations of Age and Family Composition among American Women, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Mayor, N. - Defective Parvoviruses Protect against Virally-Induced Tumors, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Baylor College of Medicine - Endocrine Fund, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Younes, M. - Development of an Animal Model for Human Endometriosis Using the Nude Mouse, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Gibbons, W. E. - Progestin Effects on Human Endometrium in Post Menopausal Estrogen Replacement, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Malinak, R. - Endometriosis in Relation to Fertility, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Goldzieher, J. - Comparison of Drugs to Induce Ovulation, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Besch, P.K. and Zamah, N. M. - Transplantation of Normal and Ectopic Human Endometrial Tissue into Athymic Nude Mice, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Moore, L. - Bilingual Health Educator, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Hays, B. - Breast Feeding Mothers' Hotline, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Hays, B. - Breast Feeding Mothers' Hotline, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Lovick, S. R. - 'Young Moms' Parent Education Program, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Meyer, J.S. - Neurology Research, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Lockshin, A. - Rapid Screening of Drugs as a Predictive Mechanism for Treating Cancer Patients, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Zamah, N. M. - A Comparison of the Tissue Effects of the CO2 Laser and Electrosurgery in Infertility Surgery, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Elkind-Hirsch, K. - Treatment of Infertility with Pulsatile LHRH Administration: Intravenous vs. Subcutaneous Route, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Elkind-Hirsch, K and Reynolds, Mary - Characterization and Immunoreactive GnRH and hCG Levels in Normal and Diabetic Pregnancy, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Nader, Shala - Characteristics of Patients with and without Gonadotropin Surges during Follicular Recruitment in an in vitro Fertilization/Embryo Transfer Program, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Sugarman, Barrett - Estrogens and Chlamydia Infections in Women, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Doody, Michael - Investigation of Atrial Natriuetic Factor in Female Reproduction, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Hickox, Peter G. - Characterization of the Optimum Estrogen/Progesterone Combination for Hormonal Replacement Therapy in the Postmenopausal Female, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Goldzieher, Joseph W. - Use of Megestrol Acetate for the Destruction of Uterine Fibromyomas, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Lovell A. and McCamant, Susan - Evaluation of Progesterone-Induced Increase in Estradiol Dehydronenase as a Practical Test for Prediction of Hormonal Responsiveness, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Chocko, Mariam - Ethnic and Age Differences in Prevalence Rates of Sexually Transmitted Diseases Among Adolescent Females, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Weitzman, Glenn - Trans-Hysteroscopic Intra-Fallopian Gamete Transfer, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Dunn, Randall C. - Study of Efficacy of Nafareline Acetate and Tissue Plasminogen Activator in the Prevention of Post-operative Adhesions in an Animal Model, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Storthz, Karen - Viruses as Etiologic Agents of Genital Cancer, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nader, Shala - A Study of Female Fecundity, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Krasnow, Joel - Investigation of the Hormonal Regulation of Aromatase in the Developing Follicle and Corpus Luteum, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Winkel, Craig - Modulation of Vascular Endothelial Cell Cholesterol Metabolism by Sex Steroids, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Pivarnik, James - Effect of Menstrual Cycle Phase on Serum Creatine Kinase Levels Following Endurance Exercise, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Brody, Steven A. - The Study of Neuroendocrine Mechanisms in the Control of Hypothalamic GnRH Secretory Activity in Vivo and in Vitro, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Snabes, Michael - The Safety and Efficacy of Aspirin in the Prevention of Pregnancy-Induced Hypertension, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Hinkley, Clark - Loan Repayment Program for Nurse-midwifery Education, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Newmark, Michael - Two Part Education and Research Project to Help Epileptic Women Manage Their Pregnancies, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Valdes, Cecilia - Late Onset Congenital Adrenal Hyperplasia: Hormonal and DNA Diagnosis in Women with Various Gynecologic Disorders, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Whitworth, Tina - Evaluation to Determine if Endometrial Thickness, Endometrial Growth, and Dominant Follicular Growth are Predictors of Implantation, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Brody, Steven A. - Pathophysiological Studies on Tissue Injury and Adhesion Formation Following Laser, Thermal, and Electrosurgical Cauterization, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Nadar, Shala - Study of the Absorption and Bioavailability of Sublingually Administered Progesterone Lozenges, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Hays, Bethany - A Request for Funds for A Women's Retreat for the Baylor OB-GYN Residents, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Bakht, Fred R. - Prevalence of Toxoplasmosis in Young Women: A Cross Sectional Serologic Survey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Fisher, Jeanne - Breastfeeding Peer Counselor Program, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Snabes, Michael - The Use of Human Eggs as a Model for DNA Analysis: How Sex Steroid Hormones Regulate Carbohydrate Metabolism, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Hergenroeder, Albert C. - The Effect of Estrogen Therapy on Osteopenia, Stress Fractures, and the Risk of Osteoporosis in Young Women with Hypothalamic Amenorrhea, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Mann, Melinda S. - Diseases of the Vulva and Vagina: Slide Library Project, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Chuong, C. James - Effects of Naloxone on Luteinizing Hormone Secretion in Premenstrual Syndrome, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - McFarlane, Judith - De Madres a Madres Program, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Bynum, Diane - Expecting the Best Healthy Baby Kit, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Sherman, Lori - How Sex Steroid Hormones Regulate Carbohydrate Metabolism, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Dunn, Randall C. - An Experimental Model to Study the Etiology and Development of Endometriosis, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Ritchie, Karen S. - A Mental Health Program for Breast Cancer Patients, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Cowles, Tracy - Association of Placental Chromosomes Abnormalities with Abnormal Pregnancy Outcome, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cassin, Kristi Shipnes - Community Partners, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Grant Writing, The Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - A & M Alkek Foundation, 1999; 2001; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Aetna Foundation, 2011 - 2012 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - AIM Foundation, 2000 – 2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Albert and Ethel Herzstein Charitable Foundation, 1999 – 2009 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Alcoa Foundation, 2011 - 2012 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Allbritton Foundation, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Alpha Phi Foundation, Walgreen, 2005; 2012 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - AMA Health Literacy Grant, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Anne and CW Duncan Jr. Foundation, 1998; 2001-2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Anneberg Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Atofina Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Baxter – Whalen Family Foundation, 2000; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bridgeway Foundation, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Build – A – Bear – Bear Hugs Foundation, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Burlington Resources, 1999 - 2000; 2002 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - CIGNA Foundation, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Cockrell Foundation, 1991; 1994; 1997; 1999; 2000-2001; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - CRC Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Cullen Foundation, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Daisy Foundation, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Daughters of Charity Foundation, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Denman Foundation, 2001 – 2009 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Dishman Charitable Trust Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Do Net Research, Foundation Directory Online, 2003- 2004; 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Duke Energy, 1993; 1997; 2000; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - e Women Network Foundation, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - El Paso Energy, 2000-2003; 2006 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Esphahanian Foundation, 2003 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Estill Foundation, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Exxon Mobile Foundation, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Florence S. Ducey Charity Trust, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Florence and William K. McGee, Jr. Family Foundation, 2001; 2003; 2005; 2008 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Frees Foundation, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Frees Foundation, 1997; 2001; 2005-2006; 2009 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Galen T. Brown Foundation, 2002; 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Gus and Karen Comiskey Foundation, 2003 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Hackett Family Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Halliburton II, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Harris County Medical Society Alliance, 1989; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Harry S. and Isabel C. Cameron Foundation, 1998 – 1999; 2000 – 2001; 2003- 2005 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Humana Communities Benefit Grant, 2010 – 2011 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - J.A. and Isabel M. Elkins Foundations, 1997; 1999; 2001; 2002; 2004 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - John and Linda Knox Family Foundation, 2001; 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - John M. O' Quinn Foundation, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - John W. and Ann K. Johnson Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Judi and Jack Holmes Foundation, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Kinder Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - LIATIS Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Life Time Fitness Foundation, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Light Charitable Trust, 2003 – 2004 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Lillie H. and Joseph D. Jamail Foundation, 2001 - 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Local Independent Charities of America (LICA), 2006 – 2008 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Lowe Foundation, 1992 - 1995; 2002; 2004 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Manning Foundation, 2001; 2003; 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - M.D Anderson Foundation, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Margaret and James A. Elkins, Jr. Foundation, 1997-1998; 2000 – 2003 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Neva and Wesley West Foundation, 1995; 1997-1999; 2001; 2003 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - O' Neil Foundation, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Paul and Mary Haas Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Previous Funding History, 1984 – 1985; 1987-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Ralph and Eileen Swett Foundation, 2009; 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Raymond and Susan Brochstein Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Robert W. Sr. and Pearl Wallis Knox Foundation, 1991- 1993; 1998- 2005; 2008 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Shell Foundation, 1992; 1999; 2000; 2001; 2003 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Stedman West Foundation, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Susan Vaughan Foundation – Financial report, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - The Barnard Foundation, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - The Blackwell Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - The Bob and Cathleen Davis Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - The Chapman Foundation, 2006 – 2009 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - The Charles and Melissa Davis Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - The Children's Fund, Inc., 1999 – 2001 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - The Clarence Westbury Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - The Dunham Charitable Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - The Durham Foundation, 2001 – 2002 – Check (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - The Gordon and Mary Cain Foundation, 2000-2001; 2004-2005; 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - The Hoglund Foundation, 1994; 1996-1997; 2002; 2004-2005; 2007-2011 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - The Jackson Foundation, 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - The Jackson Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - The JBD Foundation, 2001; 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - The John C and Nan K Willett Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - The Journey Foundation, 2002 – 2004 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - The Meadows Foundation, 2003; 2010; 2011 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - The McGovern Fund for the Behavioral Sciences, 1990; 1992 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - The Powell Foundation, 1999; 2000-2003; 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - The Prudential Foundation, 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - The Trammell Foundation, 1997-2005 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - The W.T. and Louise J. Moran Foundation, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - The Woodhill Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Trotter Education Foundation, 2003; 2005 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - United Health Foundation, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - United Way, 2003- 2004; 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Vale - Asche Foundation, 1998 – 1999; 2001 – 2004; 2008 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Waggoners Foundation, 2001 – 2003 (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Walgreens Foundation, 2010-2012 (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Watson Family Foundation, 2001; 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - W. J Bowen Foundation, 2004 – 2005 (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - Denied-Houston Local Organizing Committee (LOC) Grant submission, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - The Hoglund Foundation, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Grant Recipient Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Grant History, 1980-2003; 2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Wendy Haskell Meyer Endowment, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Rockwell Fund, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Susan Vaughan Foundation, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Grant Materials (Program & Financials), 2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Durham Foundation, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)